A Guide to the Francis O. Holmes papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA129
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence, 1924-1979; 1; 8.4 Cubic Feet
  - Gad-Ganc (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - B.M. Gaddis, 1944
    - Amy Gage, 1952
    - C. Gainor, 1968
    - D. Carleton Gajdusek, 1962 1964 1966 1968 1973
    - W.R. Galbrath, 1961-1963
    - Rogdrigo Gamez, 1968
    - S. Gancayco, 1961
  - Gano-Gasi (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - R. Ganora, 1934
    - R.J. Garber, 1950
    - M.R. Garcia, 1946
    - W.W. Garner, 1935
    - F.H. Garrison, 1934
    - H.L. Gaschen, 1926-1927 1936 1938
    - E.C. Gasiokiewicz, 1952 1956
  - Gasser, Herbert S., 1939 1944 1946 1948 1950-1953 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Gat-Ger (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - L.F. Gates, 1959
    - H. Zanyin Gaw, 1947-1949
    - Q. Geiman, 1932
    - Genetics Citation Index, 1963
    - J.A. George, 1961
    - D.U. Gerstel, 1945-1946
  - Gid-Gle (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - N.J. Giddings, 1932 1936 1943 1950 1954
    - Robert S. Gill, 1947-1949 1954
    - I.C. Gillam, 1960-1961
    - Robert M. Gilmer, 1958
    - P. Gisquet, 1953
    - Otto Glaser, 1945
    - S. Glasstone, 1941
    - H.A. Gleason, 1937-1938
  - God-Goh (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Alexander Gode, 1956-1959 1961 1963-1965 1969
    - Austin C. Gohcen, 1952-1953
  - Goi-Gou (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - G. Goidanich, 1958
    - David H. Goodchild, 1955
    - Kenneth Goodner, 1939
    - Ernest W. Goodpasture, 1928 1948
    - T. Harper Goodspeed, 1937-1939
    - L.J. Goss, 1942
    - R.W. Goss, 1928 1932 1940
    - C.J. Gould, 1955 1957-1958 1963-1965
  - Gra-Greene (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Thomas Grace, 1957
    - A.A. Granovsky, 1928
    - G.P. Grant, 1931
    - Madeleine P. Grant, 1947
    - Theodore J. Grant, 1932-1933 1936-1939 1942 1947 1952-1953 1957
    - Carl O. Grassl, 1953
    - G.F. Gravatt, 1955
    - Arthur H. Graves, 1954
    - Gray Herbarium, 1938
    - Joseph E. Greaves, 1926
    - Wyman R. Green, 1942-1943
    - J. Greenberg, 1961
    - Jennifer Greene, 1970
  - Walter H. Greenleaf, 1945 1946 1950-1953 1956 1959 1962 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Grel-Hab (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Tadeusz B. Grela, 1958 1960
    - E.A. Griffiths, 1963
    - E.S. Griggs, 1933
    - Grace H. Griswold, 1941
    - R.G. Grogan, 1962
    - E. Grunberg, 1961
    - E.F. Guba, 1939 1954-1955
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1953 1963 1965-1966
    - M. Gunasekaran, 1965
    - Carl E.F. Guterman, 1939
    - J. Dennett Guthrie, 1956
    - Cushman Haagensen, 1951
    - Frank A. Haasis, 1931
    - E.S. Haber, 1959
  - Conrad M. Haenseler, 1931 1935-1942 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Conrad M. Haenseler, 1943-1947 1949-1954 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Hag-Hann (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - W.A.F. Hagborg, 1959
    - D.G. Hagedorn, 1950 1953-1954 1957
    - Nicholas Hahon, 1961
    - M.C. Hall, 1927
    - D.L. Hallock, 1961
    - James I. Hambleton, 1925 1946-1947 1951
    - S. Hamid Mahmood, 1964
    - James M. Hamilton, 1950-1952
    - C.E. Hammond, 1942
    - Dorothy Hammond, 1941
    - Handbook of Biological Data, 1955
    - H.R. Hamner, 1958
    - Chancellor I. Hannan, 1957
  - Hans-Harra (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - John R. Hansbrough, 1952-1954 1956
    - A.J. Hansen, 1968
    - Henning P. Hansen, 1955-1956
    - E.D. Hansing, 1942
    - J.H. Happ, 1969-1970
    - Chris Hardy, 1971
    - R.A. Harper, 1926
    - J.G. Harrar, 1956-1957
  - Harris-Harrison (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - R.V. Harris, 1933-1934 1937 1955 1960-1961
    - A.L. Harrison, 1943 1952
    - B.D. Harrison, 1963
  - Hart-Hartz (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Helen Hart, 1945-1951
    - William Hartley, 1962-1963
    - Albert Hartzell, 1933 1943
  - Harv-Hat (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - R.B. Harvey, 1942-1943
    - R.J. Haskell, 1928
    - H. Hasselriis, 1956
    - Leonard Hatton, 1959
  - Hea-Hei (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - A.F. Hean, 1939
    - Cannon C. Hearne, 1952
    - T.T. Hebert, 1965 1961
    - Florence Hedges, 1936
    - Howard E. Heggestad, 1955 1957-1958 1963-1965
    - Robert W. Hegner, 1925 1928-1929
    - Gertrude Heidenthal, 1947
    - Carl Heinrich, 1944
    - K. Heinze, 1964
  - Hend-Hera (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - R.G. Henderson, 1929 1938 1950-1951 1953
    - Mary C. Hendrickson, 1956 1960 1964
    - Marion V. Hendrickson, 1952, undated
    - J. Walter Hendrix, 1946-1947
    - A.W. Henry, undated
    - Herald American, 1978
  - Herb-Hew (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Gustav F. Herbst, 1950-1951
    - F.J. Hermann, 1940
    - R.M. Herriott, 1965
    - William Hesketh, 1971
    - John W. Heuberger, 1931 1934
    - W.B. Hewitt, 1942
  - Hib-Hild (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Craig R. Hibben, 1971
    - M.T. Hilborn, 1957 1963
    - Earl M. Hildebrand, 1938 1940-1944 1946 1948 1952 1954-1957 1964
    - A.C.H. Hildebrandt, 1965-1966
  - Hill-Hit (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - A.V. Hill, 1942
    - John E. Hill, 1944
    - S. Hilgard, 1970
    - Marion Hines, 1964
    - H.E. Hirsch, 1952
    - George K. Hirst, 1956-1957
    - L. Hirth, 1963-1965
    - J.H. Hitchborn, 1957
    - A. Parker Hitchens, 1943-1944 1946
  - Ho-Hof (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - William Ho, 1954
    - Charles L. Hoagland, 1940
    - Albion Hodgon, 1969-1973
    - Loren J. Hoffbeck, 1962
    - James C. Hoffman, 1947
    - W.H. Hoffman, 1943
    - Rachel E. Hoffstadt, 1937
  - Hog-Holz (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - William D. Hogan, 1949-1950
    - Isme A. Hoggan, 1931 1934-1935
    - Marshall P. Hoke, 1971
    - W.D. Holly, 1941
    - M. Hollings, 1956 1959-1960
    - John P. Hollis, Jr., 1952
    - J.K. Holohan, 1942
    - A. Holton, 1971
    - C.S. Holton, 1958
    - John W. Holzberlein, Jr., 1951
  - Hone-Honi (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Edwin E. Honey, 1950-1955
    - Hans Leo Honigmann, 1929 1931 1939-1940
  - Honm-Hop (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Shigemi Honma, 1968 1975 1977
    - M.M. Hoover, 1951 1956
    - S.L. Hopperstead, 1941
  - Horn-Hors (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Claud L. Horn, 1963
    - Norman L. Horn, 1947-1948
    - Frank L. Horsfall, 1948-1950 1956-1957 1961
    - James G. Horsfall, 1969
  - Hort-Hoy (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Mary B. Horton, 1943
    - Hotel Filipinas, 1961-1963
    - L.F. Hough, 1950
    - Ralph B. Houlihan, 1948
    - Charles L. Hovey, 1943
    - Frank L. Howard, 1941
    - Richard A. Howard, 1968
    - J.L. Howatt, 1938
    - Marshall A. Howe, 1936
    - John T. Howell, 1939
    - William G. Hoyman, 1942
  - Hua-Hug (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - P.C. Huang, 1957 1959
    - N. Hubbeling, 1960 1964
    - Wolfgang Huber, 1947
    - Leland W. Hudson, 1959-1960
    - P.S. Hudson, 1955
    - Jesse M. Huffington, 1951 1954
    - C.G. Hughes, 1956
    - Morris Hughes, 1945
  - H.B. Humphrey, 1934-1936 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - H.B. Humphrey, 1937-1940 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - H.B. Humphrey, 1941-1943 1947 1953 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Hun-Hutchins (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Chang Hsun Hung, 1956
    - Dora G. Hunt, 1957
    - N. Rex Hunt, 1946
    - Larry Huntley, 1973
    - Allan Hurff, 1941
    - Lee M. Hutchins, 1932 1936-1937 1939 1941 1945 1947-1953 1955-1958 1961
  - C.S. Hutchinson, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Martin T. Hutchinson, 1952-1953 1957-1958 1960-1964 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Hutchinson-Hy (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Mary A. Hutchinson, 1957
    - F.B. Hutt, 1953
    - E.M. Hutton, 1949-1950 1953
    - Roscoe, R. Hyde, 1936 1938-1940
    - Howard L. Hyland, 1950 1952 1963 1965
  - Id-Iri (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Idaho Agricultural Experiment Station, 1956
    - Seiitro Ikeno, 1934
    - Illinois, University of, 1966
    - Indian Bee Journal, 1964-1966
    - W.J. Ing, 1931
    - Institut Expérimental des Tabacs, 1958
    - Instituto Miguel Lillo, 1948
    - International Association of Microbiologists, 1947
    - International Atomic Energy Agency, 1962
    - International Congress for Microbiology, 1958
    - International Cooperation Administration, 1958
    - International House, 1955
    - International Rice Research Institute, 1962
    - Irish Beekeeper, 1970
  - Irw-Iz (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - M.R. Irwin, 1965
    - I. Isaac, 1963
    - Hikmet Ismen, 1957-1958
    - Isotope Committee, The Rockefeller Institute, 1960
    - Itinerary - FAO, 1961
    - Camille Izard, 1957 1962-1963
  - Ja-Jenk (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - A.L. James, 1939
    - E. James, 1965
    - Paul C. Janaske, 1961
    - Japan Agricultural College, 1934
    - Jardin Botanique, Université d'Alger, 1938
    - Pancho Jarino, 1969
    - Edwin Jayanetti, 1956
    - Elbert R. Jaycox, 1963 1968
    - Henry Jedlinski, 1953
    - Henry Jeffers, Jr., 1942-1943
    - Anna E. Jenkins, 1941
    - John E. Jenkins, 1956
    - Samuel F. Jenkins, Jr., 1965
    - Wilbert A. Jenkins, 1940
    - W.R. Jenkins, 1969
  - Jensen-Jenson (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - D.D. Jensen, 1946-1953 1958-1961
    - James H. Jensen, 1933-1934 1936-1937 1939-1940 1942-1944 1949 1951 1954-1955 1958
    - Lawrence Jenson, 1958
  - Johansson-E.M. Johnson (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - T.S.K. Johansson, 1966
    - C.A. John, 1950 1954 1957 1961-1962
    - Burt Johnson, 1931-1932
    - E.M. Johnson, 1931 1941 1945-1947 1959
  - Fo. Johnson-Fr. Johnson (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Folke Johnson, 1942 1945 1951
    - F.H. Johnson, 1941 1943
  - James Johnson, 1931 1934-1935 1937-1943 1945 1947-1952 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - L. Johnson-Johnston (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson, 1965
    - Marion A. Johnson, 1945 1950
    - Anthony Johnston, 1961
    - Ivan M. Johnston, 1937-1938 1950
  - Jon-Jul (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - John P. Jones, 1951
    - Linus H. Jones, 1946
    - Leon K. Jones, 1941-1942 1947
    - L.R. Jones, 1929
    - Philip M. Jones, 1926
    - Laxmikant Joshi, 1967-1968
    - Journal of General Microbiology, 1954-1955
    - M. Julitta, 1941
  - Kah-Kal (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Robert P. Kahn, 1954 1957 1959-1960 1963-1965
    - George Kalmbacher, 1961 1969
  - Kee-Kell (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Paul D. Keener, 1951 1953
    - August E. Kehr, 1949 1959
    - H.H. Keifer, 1962-1963
    - George W. Keitt, 1954
    - John R. Keller, 1952 1960-1961
    - Thomas S. Kelly, 1971
  - Kelm-Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Arthur Kelman, 1955 1966-1967
    - Clarence H. Kennedy, 1927
    - George C. Kent, 1950 1954-1955 1957 1964
    - E.A. Kerr, 1957
    - Arthur G. Kevorkian, 1948
    - W.G. Keyworth, 1963-1964
  - Kid-Kish (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - John G. Kidd, 1938
    - C.B. Kightlinger, 1938 1952
    - K. Kikuta, 1947
    - R.R. Kincaid, 1937 1938
    - R.C. King, 1955
    - R.S. Kirby, 1940-1941 1943 1948
    - Hari Kishore, 1959-1960
  - Kle-Kni (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - A. Kleczkowski, 1954
    - Richard M. Klein, 1957-1958
    - E. Klienberger, 1932
    - Caroline H. Klinkenberg, 1945
    - Maximilian Klinkowski, 1949 1952-1955 1958-1959 1962-1963 1965
    - B.C.J.G. Knight, 1954
    - C.A. Knight, 1949 1951 1954 1957
  - L. Carl Knorr, 1954 1956-1959 1961 1964 1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Koc-Kos (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Koch, 1937
    - Kodak, Eastman Company, 1927
    - Erich Kohler, 1939 1949 1951-1952 1956
    - Thor Kommedahl, 1964-1965 1967
    - Eugene H. Kone, 1957
    - Hilary Koprowski, 1952
    - Yukio Koshimizu, 1956
    - Dontcho Kostoff, 1936-1937
    - T. Kosuge, 1964
  - Kra-Kul (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - J.P. Kramer, 1961
    - K.W. Kreitlow, 1941 1948-1949 1951-1956 1960-1961 1965
    - Hillier Krieghbaum, 1952-1953
    - Basil Krone, 1949-1950
    - C.A. Krug, 1938-1939
    - C.W. Kuhn, 1961 1965
    - Mark R. Kulp, 1939
  - Louis O. Kunkel (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Louis O. Kunkel, 1923 1925 1931 1934-1935 1940 1942-1946
    - Louis O. Kunkel - Annual Reports, 1937-1944 1946
    - Louis O. Kunkel - Corporation Reports, 1936-1940 1942 1945 1948
  - Lach-Lal (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Rene O. Lachance, 1956
    - William H. Lachman, 1945-1946 1954-1955 1957 1960 1962
    - J. Lackett, 1970
    - Charles F. Lackey, 1932 1936
    - A. Lafont, 1935
    - S.B. Lal, 1957 1964-1965 1967
  - Lanc-Lawt (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Jack Lancaster, 1964
    - Robert W. Langhans, 1956
    - Langstroth Bee Garden, 1960
    - Lank Brothers, 1945
    - Epitacio A. Lanuza, 1961
    - R.H. Larson, 1942 1953 1957
    - Larson Brothers, 1951
    - A.M. Lasheen, 1958
    - Richard Laster, 1962
    - T.L. Latham, 1950
    - Randall Latta, 1962
    - K.W. Lauer, 1940
    - Max A. Lauffer, 1954 1956 1960
    - James Laurie, 1963
    - H. Laven, 1956
    - Roger H. Lawson, 1965
    - Elva Lawton, 1950
  - Lea-Lep (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - J.G. Leach, 1940
    - R.I. Leather, 1961-1962
    - G. Lebeurier, 1963-1965
    - Joshua Lederberg, 1951
    - S.C. Lee, 1947
    - S.G. Lehman, 1937-1938 1941
    - W. Lehman, 1930
    - W. Lener, 1963
    - C.W. Leng, 1929
    - L.B. Lent, 1942
    - E.E. Leppik
  - James W. Lesley, 1934 1939 1941-1944 1952-1957 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Less-Lew (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Erwin F. Lessel, Jr., 1956-1957
    - Roy Letsen, 1963
    - Irvin Levin, 1958
    - Michael Levine, 1937-1938
    - Paul Levine, 1962
    - Charles D. Lewis, 1960
    - F.H. Lewis, 1960
    - Lowell M. Lewis, 1973
  - Lil-Linf (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - J.H. Lilly, 1964
    - Pierre Limasset, 1948-1949 1951-1952 1954
    - Donald P. Limber, 1952
    - Ralph E. Lincoln, 1941-1942
    - Lloyd A. Lindenfelser, 1967
    - Robert C. Lindner, 1948 1950-1951 1955
    - E.W. Lindstrom, 1937 1939
    - M.B. Linford, 1939
  - Lee Ling, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Lee Ling, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Linn-Liv (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - M.B. Linn, 1936
    - Harry Lippman, 1958
    - Donald J. Lisk, 1959
    - R.M. Lister, 1960
    - Little, Brown & Company, Publishers, 1956-1957
    - Herbert E. Little, 1961-1962
    - Steven C. Liu, 1956-1957
    - J.E. Livingston, 1955
  - Loc-Lyn (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - M.M. Locke, 1938-1939
    - Seth B. Locke, 1939 1941 1945 1951 1965
    - C. Logothetis, 1961
    - Ricardo J. Lois, 1947
    - H.F. Loomis, 1935
    - Lidy Lopez, 1955
    - Hubert S. Loring, 1947 1949
    - J.C. Lotze, 1945
    - J.B. Loughnane, 1953
    - Harvey B. Lovell, 1963 1966
    - Osvaldo Lovisolo, 1958
    - W.R. Loewenstein, 1958
    - G.B. Lucas, 1955 1960
    - William H. Luman, 1930
    - Luna, 1962
    - Bernard Lupinek, 1957-1958
    - Lloyd Lynch, 1968
    - S.J. Lynch
  - MacA-MacN (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - John W. MacArthur, 1939-1940
    - W.D. MaClement, 1937
    - Joseph J. MacDonald, 1958
    - Mary G. MacIsaac, 1948
    - F.C. MacKeever, 1950
    - Alfred H. Mackenzie, 1962-1963
    - Duncan A. MacInnes, 1954
    - Justina B. MacLean, 1961
    - D.J. MacLeod, 1930-1931
    - Boyd MacNaughton, 1946
    - B.H. MacNeill, 1953
  - Mag-Mara (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Beatrice Magdoff, 1961 1964
    - A.W. Magers, 1970
    - J.R. Magness, 1948
    - Roy Magruder, 1935-1936 1940
    - Walter J. Mahoney, 1964
    - W.F. Mai, 1948 1952 1965
    - Charles C. Major, 1955-1957 1962
    - N. Makushenno, 1930
    - R.C. Malhotra, 1932
    - G.R. Mandels, 1960
    - L.F. Mandelson, 1940
    - D.C. Mandeville, 1962
    - A.J. Mangelsorf, 1944
    - William M. Mann, 1938
    - Miguel A. Manzano, 1959
    - Josef Marais, 1956
  - Karl Maramorosch, 1947-1949 1953 1957 1960 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Karl Maramorosch, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Karl Maramorosch, 1962-1964 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Karl Maramorosch, 1965-1970 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Karl Maramorosch, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - L. Maramorosch-E.C. Martin (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Lydia Maramorosch, 1963
    - A. Marani, 1963
    - E. Marcelli, 1955
    - G. Marjorana, 1966
    - Roy Markham, 1954
    - W.G. Marquette, 1926
    - David Marsden, 1957 1959-1960
    - R.W. Marsh, 1955
    - Mauro E. Martignoni, 1964
    - Arthur W. Martin, 1958
    - E.C. Martin, 1959
  - Mart-Mas (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Mark W. Martin, 1960-1961
    - W.J. Martin, 1953 1955
    - P.W. Mason, 1941 1954
  - Matt-Mayt (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Jacob Matthew, 1965
    - R.E.F. Matthews, 1941 1955
    - Harold Mattson, 1939 1941 1943
    - Takashi Matsumoto, 1938-1939
    - Mauritius Medical and Health Department, 1937
    - Curtis May, 1950 1962
    - George M.E. Mayo, 1948 1955
    - Warren W. Maytrott, 1946-1949 1951-1953 1957-1958 1965
  - McC-McK (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - S.E.A. McCallan, 1951-1953 1964-1966
    - L. McCallum, 1948
    - Lewis P. McCann, 1950-1951
    - Maclyn McCarty, 1968
    - A.P.D. McClean, 1932 1937 1947-1948 1957
    - Gilbert G. McCollum, 1966
    - D.Z. McCormick, 1952
    - F.A. McCormick, 1932
    - W.A. McCubbin, 1942
    - Margaret McCullough, 1965
    - R. Barclay McGhee, 1964
    - A.G. McGill, 1971
    - Marian McGrath, 1946
    - McIlhenny Company, 1949
    - CD. McKeen, 1951 1953
  - H.H. McKinney, 1929 1936 1939-1940 1942-1943 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - H.H. McKinney, 1944-1945 1947-1952 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - H.H. McKinney, 1953-1957 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - McL-McW (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - H.R. McLarty, 1951-1952
    - D.M. McLean, 1941
    - J.E. McMurtrey, Jr., 1955
    - George L. McNew, 1951-1953 1955 1959 1961-1962
    - Frank P. McWhorter, 1925-1926 1939 1941 1943 1947-1951 1953 1957-1958 1964
  - Med-Messi (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - John Medler, 1940
    - V.J.D. Meeuse, 1962-1963
    - F.C. Meier, 1930
    - Alfred N. Meiss, 1943
    - G. Melchers, 1941
    - James L. Melgar, 1962
    - D.R. Mendoza, 1961
    - Mario Meneghini, 1954
    - K.P.V. Menon, 1962
    - J.D. Menzies, 1952
    - I.A. Merchant, 1950-1951
    - Merck and Company, Inc., 1945 1954
    - Angel M. Mergal, 1947
    - M.J. Merrett, 1956-1957
    - G and C. Merriam Company, 1958
    - Elmer D. Merrill, 1930 1939
    - Julia S. Merrill, 1969-1972
    - W.H. Messeck, Jr., 1967-1968
    - C.M. Messiaen, 1960
  - Mic-Mit (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - C.D. Michener, 1965
    - Microcard Foundation, 1954
    - K. Miczynski, 1960
    - J.A. Milbrath, 1947
    - Florence M. Miller, 1949
    - Lawrence I. Miller, 1956-1958
    - Lawrence P. Miller, 1941
    - Lloyd A. Miller, 1958
    - Max Miller, 1971-1972
    - Patrick M. Miller, 1955
    - Paul R. Miller, 1952-1954 1958-1959 1962
    - P.J. Milles, 1942
  - Min-Miz (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Eunice T. Miner, 1951-1952
    - Roy W. Miner, 1951-1952
    - Alfred E. Mirsky, 1953 1965
    - Sonya W. Mirsky, 1970
    - Missouri Botanical Garden, 1970
    - John w. Mitchell, 1956
    - MacNeil Mitchell, 1952
    - Helen E. Mizer, 1965
  - Moe-Mow (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Henry A. Moe, 1954-1955 1957 1959 1962-1963
    - Harold N. Moldenke, 1937 1950
    - John Mondry, 1950
    - Ellen L. Moorhead, 1956-1958
    - Marta T. Morales, 1965
    - Georges Morel, 1949
    - C. Morgan, 1954
    - I.M. Morgan, 1942
    - Shuji Morita, 1955
    - Jarvis S. Morris, 1945
    - M. Morris, 1970
    - B.Y. Morrison, 1935 1937-1939 1943-1944 1947-1948 1950 1960
    - Grant D. Morse, 1971
    - C.V. Morton, 1937 1949-1950
    - A.H. Moseman, 1961-1962
    - J.G. Moseman, 1959-1960
    - P.B. Mott, 1938-1940
    - Chester Mowery, 1942
  - Mud-Mun (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - W.K. Mudie, 1961
    - Walter C. Mueller, 1964
    - C.F.W. Muesebeck, 1949
    - C.H. Muller, 1938-1940
    - R.S. Mullin, 1952 1954
    - B.B. Mundkur, 1948-1949
    - K.W. Mundry, 1961
    - G. Donald Munger, 1953
    - Henry Munger, 1945 1960
  - Mura-Murt (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Harry H. Murakishi, 1957-1958 1962-1963
    - K.C. Murdock, 1964
    - Frederick A. Murphy, 1978
    - Everitt G.D. Murray, 1943 1949-1950 1954
    - T.J. Murray, 1942
    - Y.K.S. Murthy, 1954
  - Nag-Nar (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - A.N. Nagaraj, 1960 1962-1966 1977
    - C.M. Nagel, 1947-1948
    - Aniela Namyslowska, 1927
    - T.K. Nariani, 1953 1959
  - Juan Naron, 1961-1965 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Nata-National Sci (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - K.P. Natarajan, 1966
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1965
    - National Arboretum, 1977
    - National Science Foundation, 1957 1961 1964-1965 1969
  - National Soc-Nel (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - National Society for Medical Research, 1954
    - John J. Natti, 1959
    - Navy Department, 1943
    - Radha Nayar, 1964-1965
    - A.G. Naylor, 1962
    - H.R. Nazeem, 1968
    - Neal Brothers, Inc., 1956
    - Elton G. Nelson, 1956-1957
    - F.E. Nelson, 1949-1950
    - Ray Nelson, 1933
    - Warren O. Nelson, 1961
  - New International Yearbook, 1960-1966 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Newh-Nix (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - A.G. Newhall, 1941-1942 1953 1955
    - Nelson Newton, 1949
    - New York Academy of Sciences, 1958-1960
    - New York Porto Rico Steamship, 1946
    - Niagara Chemical Division, FMC Corporation, 1962
    - J.G. Nichols, 1944
    - Ernest F. Nichols, 1944
    - L.P. Nichols, 1950
    - L.G. Nickell, 1954-1955
    - Otto Nieschulz, 1925
    - E.L. Nixon, 1950
  - Nob-Nog (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - R.J. Noble, 1939-1940 1949
    - Hideyo Noguchi, 1924-1927
  - Nol-North (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - J.A.B. Nolla, 1937-1938
    - D. Noordam, 1955
    - D.O. Norris, 1947-1952 1954 1957 1964-1965
    - Richard D. Northcraft, 1952
    - Northeastern Division, American Phytopathological Society, 1952-1953
  - Northeast Division, American Phytopathological Society, 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Norv-Nu (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Thomas J. Nugent, 1954-1956
    - Fauste L. Nuque, 1960
    - John Nutman, 1947
  - Gerardo O. Ocfemia, 1939-1940 1945-1949 1952-1957 1959 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Of-Ow (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Officer in Charge of Piers, 1963
    - Peter K. Olitsky, 1929 1947
    - Marcel Alves De Oliveira, 1948
    - Marciano O. Olivo, Sr., 1962
    - C.J. Olson, 1954
    - P.W. Oman, 1944
    - George D. O'Neill, 1960
    - Oriental Seed, 1945
    - Faustino Orillo, 1961-1962
    - Francine Orlowski, 1962
    - Mario Orsenigo, 1952-1953
    - C.R. Orton, 1931 1939-1940 1949
    - Paul B. Orvis, 1955
    - Henry T. Osborn, 1942 1947
    - John W. Oswald, 1953
    - S.H. Ou, 1962
    - F.V. Owen, 1953
  - Pac-Pal (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - R.A. Packer, 1950
    - Rodulfo P. Pacumbaba, 1965-1966
    - Elton F. Paddock, 1944 1951
    - A. Paillot, 1946
    - Pakistan Affairs, 1953
    - B.P. Pal, 1944 1947
    - Juan Palazon, 1960-1961
    - Cherie Palileo, 1961-1963
    - J. Pancho, 1961
    - G.C. Papavizas, 1966
  - Par-Pav (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - K.G. Parker, 1950-1951 1961
    - Joseph Parnas, 1952
    - G.K. Parris, 1944
    - Conrado Pascual, 1961
    - Edith M. Patch, 1951
    - T.T. Paulose, 1965
    - Jean Pavillard, 1956
  - Pea-Per (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Philip E. Pearce, 1970
    - P. Pecaut, 1959-1960
    - Emmanuel Pelaez, 1961
    - John Pelham, 1964
    - Pellett Gardens, 1970
    - S.B. Penick & Co., 1950
    - L.R. Penner, 1952
    - Bailey B. Pepper, 1943
    - H.G. Pereira, 1969
    - J. Enrique Perez, 1956 1959-1960
    - Champlain Perrault, 1952
    - Arnulf R. Persson, 1960 1964
  - Elmer L. Petersen, 1951-1953 1955 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Elmer L. Petersen, 1957-1960 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Peterson-Phil (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Nobel K. Peterson, 1966 1968
    - Charles Petrzelka, 1958
    - Barbara Phelps, 1951
    - Cornelius B. Philip, 1955 1962
    - S.H. Phillips, 1961-1962
  - Piem-Pier (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Robert L. Piemeisel, 1951
    - W.V.D. Pieris, 1959 1961-1964
  - Pir-Porte (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - N.W. Pirie, 1955
    - P.P. Pirone, 1934-1935 1965
    - A.G. Plakidas, 1941 1954
    - Plant Introduction Garden, 1961
    - Clark Poland, 1963
    - Louis P. Politi, 1951
    - Morris Pollard, 1950
    - Rafael E. Pontis Videla, 1944 1951-1952 1954 1956 1958
    - F.W. Poos, 1952
    - B.M. Popoff, 1961
    - William S. Porte, 1944
  - C. Porter-R. Porter (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Clark A. Porter, 1952-1953 1955 1957
    - D.R. Porter, 1939 1941-1944
    - R. Howard Porter, 1929 1948
  - Pos-Pou (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - A.F. Posnette, 1952 1954-1955 1959
    - Glenn S. Pound, 1944 1947 1953-1958 1961-1962
  - Pra-Price (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - M.K. Prasad, 1964
    - R. Prasada, 1951 1953
    - I.W. Prentice, 1951-1952 1958
    - W.A. Price, 1951
  - William C. Price, 1930 1944-1949 (Box 15, Folder 12)